Ela's family is visiting for a few days
Are you ok guys? Do you want veggies?
It took forever to make these potatoes.
We're ready here, right?
Yes.
I was talking to your mother, not yo you
One more?
Yea, more
Perfect.
Well, good job.
Yep.
Yeah they're not too super straight but we can fix that later.
Oh wow,
Why did you put a cross?
It helps to rise?
not really, it's just how it's done
Look carefully, come here.
We need to put some soil, a little, a little flowers.
Okay, right.
Yeah.
Yes! Well done!
No, I'm thinking about the bigger one.
Anto, can I taste the sugar?
When I worked in the bakery I have to fill these with yellow creams to cut them through
Wow, they are delicious.
Wow, look at that!
Look at this, they're perfect!
Said by someone who's already worked in a pastry shop.
Wow.
So we say perfect and you have to work with it.
For years and years he traveled around, he encountered elephants, lions, bad people, and some good people too.
And eventually, he met your sister
Hey girls!
Hey, do you want to go on tour?
Hi mommy
Come in!
Hi!
What language does he speak?
English.. ah no he speaks Italian
He wrote a book in Italian
Sugar?
and radish
And gogos
And you get some sugar back
This is very good exchange.
they're not really warm
they should be eaten warm?
In Dutch we call them "Berliner bollen"
Oh so they're like Krapfen
I'll switch the switch out the thing.
the blue berries, I think they might be later
Uh
These might come out maybe in June still to be edible.
This is a cross between uh raspberry and um... blueberry?
blackberry
They are a bit difficult to separate, but they make a good jam because you won't have a very nice shape by the time you get them off.
Okay.
But they make a good jam.
Strawberries
Check, there are a lot of strawberries in the garden now.
Of course.
Some yosta berries here.
They would also ripen in the coming month
This is a mixture of gooseberries and currants.
This is a very good berry.
Okay.
And leave some wilde strawberries for Ela, it's a new experience for her
so this one goes up here, and then I think, here it makes a weird corner
And it comes out there.
So it's only two meters, two and a half meters.
So where we put the vacuum needs to be a good suction point, like a good...
contact
Block it here so it doesn't go anywhere.
Okay, if you hold the vacuum cleaner I'm gonna push it through.
Let's see if it works.
Should I start going woooo?
Yeah
it worked?
and now?
Well hold it.
Uh yeah.
Yeah, you can take it out.
Okay.
So I'm gonna... I can just break this?
Yeah.
Now I'm gonna connect a slightly stronger wire and push through.
it's still there? OK
Okay
wait... go
Yep, it'shere.
yaaaay, great!
I'll connect that to the fish tape.
Yeah, they call it fish tape that thing.
And then in there
Okay that turned out well in the end.
I remember there was an awkward curve there in the black pipe that's in the wall, that's going around the lintel.
I couldn't get through it with the fish tape, which uh is this one but we fixed it with...
very thin wire and then a piece of plastic. You put that in and then vacuum from the other side and the plastic will create a vacuum in the pipe and pull through this very thin...
wire, very light and with that you can pull through a larger piece of cord and then the fish tape and that's how it works
Once the fish tape's connected to these wires you can actually pull quite hard b
It's all very much into the stone, so yeah, turned out well.
The rest will be much easier
Hood.
Red hood, yeah.
I think we can buy more plants.
This is Beetroot.
Can go a bit closer, I think.
This is just the leaves, right?
Yeah, they go just the leaves.
Rainbow.
It's gonna be super colorful like blue, purple...
Oh, hairy...
That's guys.
Okay.
Alright, almost all the lights are in.
Two more spotlights have to go in on the top here and the two in the...
There's also lights in the little niches in the wall.
But um yeah 14... no 16 spotlights
LEDs and one pendant over there.
Planning to make something nice of the cover.
Um
And obviously how it hangs up over the beam that needs to change as well.
It's just a temporary setup but yeah it's nice to finally see light in here.
So there's light on all the workbenches and especially on the main workbench in the middle
Actually that can go even brighter.
It has a separate switch, but I have to unpack it.
Yeah, then an outdoor light here Which I can also switch but yeah everything is working so I'm gonna
Breaker switches there, with the groups coming in so I can isolate the lights, sockets, and machines, they're separated
uh protected by breakers, so good it's it's all working.
Starting to rain again.